"use strict";
Object.defineProperty(exports, "__esModule", { value: true });
exports.cardsProgramming = exports.cardsCapitals = exports.setsData = void 0;
exports.setsData = [
    {
        id: "65971bf211b1482496d19395",
        title: "Learn the capitals",
        description: "Learn the capitals of the world with this set!",
        author: "Ali",
        private: false,
        cards: 10,
    },
    {
        id: "65971bf211b1482496d19397",
        title: "Learn Programming Languages",
        description: "Learn all the programming languages and acronyms!",
        author: "Mehmet",
        private: false,
        cards: 10,
    },
];
exports.cardsCapitals = [
    {
        question: "Which country is the city of Tokyo located in?",
        answer: "Japan",
        set: "65971bf211b1482496d19395",
    },
    {
        question: "Which country is the city of Paris located in?",
        answer: "France",
        set: "65971bf211b1482496d19395",
    },
    {
        question: "Which country is the city of Nairobi located in?",
        answer: "Kenya",
        set: "65971bf211b1482496d19395",
    },
    {
        question: "Which country is the city of Sydney located in?",
        answer: "Australia",
        set: "65971bf211b1482496d19395",
    },
    {
        question: "Which country is the city of Rio de Janeiro located in?",
        answer: "Brazil",
        set: "65971bf211b1482496d19395",
    },
    {
        question: "Which country is the city of Cairo located in?",
        answer: "Egypt",
        set: "65971bf211b1482496d19395",
    },
    {
        question: "Which country is the city of Moscow located in?",
        answer: "Russia",
        set: "65971bf211b1482496d19395",
    },
    {
        question: "Which country is the city of Toronto located in?",
        answer: "Canada",
        set: "65971bf211b1482496d19395",
    },
    {
        question: "Which country is the city of Lima located in?",
        answer: "Peru",
        set: "65971bf211b1482496d19395",
    },
    {
        question: "Which country is the city of Beijing located in?",
        answer: "China",
        set: "65971bf211b1482496d19395",
    },
];
exports.cardsProgramming = [
    {
        question: "Which programming language is known for its use in web development and has a popular framework called 'Express.js'?",
        answer: "JavaScript (Node.js)",
        set: "65971bf211b1482496d19397",
    },
    {
        question: "Which language is known for its concurrency model and channels?",
        answer: "Go (or Golang)",
        set: "65971bf211b1482496d19397",
    },
    {
        question: "Which language uses the 'Rails' framework for web development?",
        answer: "Ruby",
        set: "65971bf211b1482496d19397",
    },
    {
        question: "What does the acronym 'API' stand for?",
        answer: "Application Programming Interface",
        set: "65971bf211b1482496d19397",
    },
    {
        question: "Which programming language is often associated with scientific computing, data analysis, and machine learning?",
        answer: "Python",
        set: "65971bf211b1482496d19397",
    },
    {
        question: "What does the acronym 'SQL' stand for?",
        answer: "Structured Query Language",
        set: "65971bf211b1482496d19397",
    },
    {
        question: "Which programming language has a mascot named 'Camel'?",
        answer: "Perl",
        set: "65971bf211b1482496d19397",
    },
    {
        question: "What does the acronym 'IDE' stand for in software development?",
        answer: "Integrated Development Environment",
        set: "65971bf211b1482496d19397",
    },
    {
        question: "Which language was primarily developed by Microsoft and is known for its '.NET' framework?",
        answer: "C#",
        set: "65971bf211b1482496d19397",
    },
    {
        question: "What does the acronym 'OOP' stand for in programming?",
        answer: "Object-Oriented Programming",
        set: "65971bf211b1482496d19397",
    },
];
//# sourceMappingURL=seed.js.map